# SYMÉON DE ALMEIDA

symeon.dealmeida@gmail.com | 0466 186 890

## **PERSONNAL INFO**

#### **Linkedin**

linkedin.com/in/symeon-dealmeida/

#### Address

1 Waterford Court, 4217 Bundall

## **KEY SKILLS**

- Programming
- · Computer use
- Customer relationship
- Communication
- Time management

#### **QUALIFICATIONS**

- Full international driving license
- Responsible Service of Alcohol

# **LANGUAGES**

French - Native English - IELTS C1

#### **INTERESTS**

- Photography
- Parkour
- Drawing
- Travel
- Hiking

# **SUMMARY**

Recently graduated from a two year study in Information Technology in France, I came in Australia to further developp my skills and experience Australia. I am appreciated for my rigor, my composure, and adapt and learn with rapidity and ease. I am available every day for the whole day, early or late shifts included and motivated to work in your company. I am looking for up to 24hours a week.

## **CAREER HISTORY**

#### Lead Developer - Internship at Countact SAS

October 2022 - January 2023

- Managed team of three employees in the accomplishment of their missions, notably by means of bi-weekly points.
- Developed a tool for company's project management on Notion, to facilitate client communication and feedback.

# Shop assistant at Le parfum du pain

October 2022 - January 2023

- Sold products, welcomed and accompanied customers throughout their purchases.
- Opened, did the restocking and closed the shops on different shifts.
- Sold and helped in intense rush period for Christmas and new year's Eve.

## Waiter at L'Incongrue

July 2022 - January 2023

- · Welcomed customers and accompanied them through their meal.
- Cleaned, cleared and set tables, took orders and assisted in cleaning dishes and equipment.
- Presented bills, processed payments and handled guests inquiries with efficiency and professionalism.

# **EDUCATION**

# **Southern Cross University**

Bachelor of Information technology,

## **IUT2 - Université Grenoble Alpes, France**

DUT Informatique, Graduated 2022